export const set4 = [
  // 4 single digits
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "25", "17", "22"],
    answer: "25"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "28", "30", "23"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["28", "20", "31", "26"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["16", "21", "27", "23"],
    answer: "23"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["14", "17", "19", "22"],
    answer: "19"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">3</div>
          <div class="row">1</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["19", "12", "21", "16"],
    answer: "19"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["24", "19", "27", "31"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["33", "26", "21", "28"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["25", "13", "18", "20"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["16", "24", "28", "21"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  // 5 single digits
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="row">3</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["27", "15", "23", "20"],
    answer: "23"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["31", "24", "36", "29"],
    answer: "31"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["34", "22", "27", "29"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["25", "32", "37", "30"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["41", "29", "36", "34"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["32", "39", "27", "34"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["34", "27", "39", "32"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["23", "28", "30", "35"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["24", "29", "31", "36"],
    answer: "31"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "22", "34", "27"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  // 8 single digits
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">3</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "47", "40", "45"],
    answer: "47"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "35", "42", "40"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["50", "45", "57", "52"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "57", "45", "50"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">1</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "44", "46", "51"],
    answer: "46"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["43", "50", "55", "48"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["40", "45", "47", "52"],
    answer: "47"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["61", "49", "56", "54"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">3</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["48", "53", "41", "46"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">5</div>
          <div class="row">4</div>
          <div class="row">6</div>
          <div class="row">7</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">9</div>
          <div class="row">8</div>
          <div class="row">2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["54", "49", "42", "47"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  // 5 double digits
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">85</div>
          <div class="row">62</div>
          <div class="row">74</div>
          <div class="row">65</div>
          <div class="row">85</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["412", "297", "371", "345"],
    answer: "371"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">66</div>
          <div class="row">42</div>
          <div class="row">35</div>
          <div class="row">92</div>
          <div class="row">46</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["281", "214", "329", "267"],
    answer: "281"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">25</div>
          <div class="row">26</div>
          <div class="row">34</div>
          <div class="row">56</div>
          <div class="row">92</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["298", "245", "167", "233"],
    answer: "233"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">26</div>
          <div class="row">82</div>
          <div class="row">94</div>
          <div class="row">22</div>
          <div class="row">55</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["342", "279", "211", "276"],
    answer: "279"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">82</div>
          <div class="row">72</div>
          <div class="row">56</div>
          <div class="row">16</div>
          <div class="row">64</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["224", "357", "290", "288"],
    answer: "290"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">45</div>
          <div class="row">62</div>
          <div class="row">74</div>
          <div class="row">45</div>
          <div class="row">24</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["250", "316", "187", "263"],
    answer: "250"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">52</div>
          <div class="row">75</div>
          <div class="row">64</div>
          <div class="row">52</div>
          <div class="row">61</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["368", "237", "304", "291"],
    answer: "304"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">83</div>
          <div class="row">92</div>
          <div class="row">52</div>
          <div class="row">28</div>
          <div class="row">17</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["337", "272", "198", "255"],
    answer: "272"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">36</div>
          <div class="row">24</div>
          <div class="row">18</div>
          <div class="row">29</div>
          <div class="row">32</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["104", "152", "139", "187"],
    answer: "139"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">52</div>
          <div class="row">25</div>
          <div class="row">73</div>
          <div class="row">64</div>
          <div class="row">42</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["256", "189", "322", "267"],
    answer: "256"
  }
];
